One thing that sets me apart from them is I don't have an establishment point of view on foreign policy.
That was so, I know what you said.
Did y'all hear what she said?
Did you read between the lines?
Did you hear what she said?
Because there were lines there.
I hope you could read.
And I have experience.
My two opponents don't have the broad experience in foreign policy that Barbara Lee has.
And they don't connect it to domestic policy here at home.
What distinguishes me is, yeah, I voted against that authorization to use force right after 9-11.
And I'm calling for a ceasefire, a permanent ceasefire now, because you can't tell me Israel's security is secured by killing 25,000-plus civilians in Gaza.
And I believe in the security of Israel and condemn the Hamas attacks.
My opponents have not called for a permanent ceasefire, but I'm going to tell you, the pathway to peace and security for the Israelis and the Palestinians can only be through a diplomatic settlement.
And it's got to include the regions in the world.